Endia Williams

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Portfolio

endia.dev

github.com/endiawilliams

Contact

✓ contact@endia.dev

in linkedin.com/in/endia-dev

3 631-948-4568

• Kansas City, MO 64133

Summary

I'm a full-stack engineer with a passion for responsive design & dynamic code. Having both a creative & a scientific turn of mind, I enjoy every part of the development process from start to finish. My diverse background gives me experience cooperating & communicating with a wide variety of people & allows me to see many perspectives. I take pride in what I do & always deliver the most efficient & elegant code possible.

Skills

Proficient

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Git & GitHub

Basic

Python, Docker

Experience

Client Coordinator

FrontStreet Facility Solutions, Ronkonkoma, NY (2018-2019)

- Assisted retail clients in securing plumbers & handymen for cost-effective repair service.
- Provided detailed & accurate quotes up to \$5,000 for plumbing & facilities repairs to clients & followed up with store managers to ensure completion.
- Maintained constant communication with supervisors & coworkers to ensure all parties were informed of progress & every effort was made to ensure service within 24 hours.

Shift Lead

Speedway Convenience Store, Wading River, NY (2017-2018)

- Processed transactions, maintained store cleanliness & assisted customers as needed to ensure prompt service.
- Accepted additional responsibilities such as keeping track of inventory & supervising up to 3 additional employees when management was absent.

Data Entry Clerk

The American Legion, Indianapolis, IN (2014-2016)

• Entered data for 1000s of paper-based member records into a custom database, ensuring that information was entered with few to no errors & submitted in a timely manner.

Education

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly (2020)

Liberal Arts

Ivy Tech Community College, Indianapolis, IN (2013-2014)

Projects

Minesweeper

Created a Minesweeper clone utilizing mutual recursion with vanilla JavaScript.

BetterCupid DevOps

Created a full-stack React app with full CRUD functionality, implemented CI/CD & deployed backend to Google Cloud.